<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><?xml-stylesheet type="text/xml" href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xslt.xml"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><generator uri="http://jekyllrb.com" version="3.3.1">Jekyll</generator><link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="http://localhost:4000/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2017-01-04T07:04:35-08:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000//</id><title type="html">A</title><subtitle>A blog on innovation in information technology  with a special emphasis on machine learning, security, automotive and other stuff from my professional life.</subtitle><author><name>Armin Wasicek</name><email>hellospencer@gmail.com</email></author><entry><title type="html">2015 Automotive Security Panorama</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/automotive/security/2015/12/24/automotive-security-panorama/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="2015 Automotive Security Panorama" /><published>2015-12-24T00:00:00-08:00</published><updated>2015-12-24T00:00:00-08:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/automotive/security/2015/12/24/automotive-security-panorama</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/automotive/security/2015/12/24/automotive-security-panorama/">&lt;p&gt;2015 has been an exciting year regarding automotive security. Many autosec incidents have been reported in media and thus raised public awareness for the field. Some of these incidents triggered big time events. It has been the first time that car makers were pointed out by name because of their vulnerable models. The first cyber security related callback action has happened in 2015. Exploits have been disclosed in mainstream security conferences such as Black Hat and Defcon and stirred up a discussion on ethical disclosure in automotive security.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;autosec-incidents-2015&quot;&gt;AutoSec incidents 2015&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/2015_autosec_events.png&quot; alt=&quot;Checkmate&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;diagnostic-interface-penetration-testing&quot;&gt;Diagnostic Interface Penetration testing&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The year started with a hack on an OBD dongle used by the Progressive insurance company. The use of OBD dongles is increasing as it can be used to retrofit older cars to the Connected Car age. The autosec researcher performing this hack said that this particular device “basically uses no security technologies whatsoever”. Most likely, this applies to other OBD dongles as well.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;man-in-the-middle-of-a-connected-car&quot;&gt;Man-in-the-middle of a Connected Car&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Next BMW cars were targeted by a  relay attack. A fake cellular station was used to intercept the connection between the ConnectedDrive and a mobile phone issuing commands, e.g., to unlock the doors. On that occasion BMW demonstrated its Over-the-Air (OTA) capabilities for the first time and responded with updating its fleet remotely. The patch included encrypting the vulnerable connection.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;remote-controlling-a-connected-car&quot;&gt;Remote Controlling a Connected Car&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After some silence, the automotive security world was hit by the report of two automotive security researchers remote controlling a Jeep Cherokee with a Wired reporter on board. They managed to intrude the vehicle through its Connect, a device to connect the vehicle to the internet. The device was reachable through its IP address and the researchers could inject some malware to invoke window lifts, braking, etc. This event caught big attention in the community and in public. It triggered a manufacturer’s first call-back action because of cyber security concerns.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;intercepting-the-connected-car&quot;&gt;Intercepting the Connected Car&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Onstar hack in the same month requires a physical device, the ‘OwnStar’ to be planted somewhere underneath a car’s body. It then uses its wireless capabilities to trick a driver’s phone into connecting. When the driver logs into the Onstar RemoteLink app, the device reads the user’s credentials and transmits those to the attacker. Using the driver’s credential, the attacker has full access to the driver’s Onstar system and can do anything that a legitimate user can do. From that point the OwnStar box is not needed anymore and can be removed from the car.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;automotive-penetration-testing-and-patching&quot;&gt;Automotive Penetration Testing and Patching&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Tesla has been targeted several times this year. Besides its corporate bounty program, two automotive security incidents went public: First, Chinese researchers claimed to be able to open the doors during driving the car. On this incident, not many details are available. In the second effort, researchers did some long term testing of the attack surface. Using physical access through an Ethernet port, they were able to access the internal network. From there on, they could use their internet security skills to hack into the internally used WebKit web browser and the internally deployed Ubuntu Linux. Altogether six vulnerabilities were found and patched through Tesla’s OTA capabilities.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;crypto-cracking-to-unlock-cars&quot;&gt;Crypto cracking to Unlock Cars&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Cracking the Megamos crypto chip has already happened in 2013, but this year the court order preventing the publication has expired in August. The Megamos chip is being deployed in immobilisers of many brands (Audi, Fiat, Honda, Volkswagen and Volvo). An immobilizer is an anti-theft device which prevents the engine of the vehicle from starting when the corresponding transponder (key) is not present. Exploiting this vulnerability exposes many vehicles to theft. The researchers were able to recover the 96-bit secret key by listening to the wireless communication of the transponder with the vehicle.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;insider-attacks-on-emissions-control-systems&quot;&gt;Insider Attacks On Emissions Control Systems&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Volkswagen DieselGate is a classic example of an insider attack: Insiders misuses their privileges to trick their peers. In the #DieselGate, the Volkswagen misused the trust its customers and regulatory bodies put into the company to deliver vehicles according to their specification. Volkswagen’s cars were not able to deliver that. On the contrary, they implemented a ‘deceit device’ which actively concealed the emission rating during test conditions. Academic researchers uncovered the plot, bringing the entire Volkswagen group in turmoil.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;hack-to-increase-e-vehicle-range&quot;&gt;Hack to increase E-Vehicle Range&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The second BMW automotive security incident this year targeted the i3 which is the company’s electric model. If equipped with a range-extender, it stores a gasoline in its tank. Due to legislative differences, in California a zero-emission vehicle is only allowed a 1.9-gallon fuel tank, whereas European owner might in 2.4 gallons. Some US i3 owners claim to have found a software hack to unlock the half gallon from the European model. Both types of cars origin from the same assembly line in Leipzig. It makes sense for the manufacturer to build a generic i3 and then fit it to the respective market by switching the software configuration. We can expect to see more of this type of attack in the future, when software is increasingly deployed to customize vehicles.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;state-trooper-vehicle-penetration-test&quot;&gt;State Trooper Vehicle Penetration Test&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Virginia’s state police has been collaborated with researchers for a penetration test of their Impala Police Interceptors. The researchers could access the vehicle bus and read and write commands that trigger actuators in the vehicle.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;airbag-hack&quot;&gt;Airbag hack&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Finally, researchers claimed to have performed a zero-day exploit to disable airbags on Audi And potentially other VolkswagenGroup vehicles. They hacked a diagnostic tool to get access to the vehicles functions. The increasing number of software tools that connect to vehicles open another, new door for attackers to get to the vehicle. Requiring a certain privileges to operate, diagnostic tools could be increasingly targeted as other attack surfaces are being locked down.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;where-is-automotive-security-going&quot;&gt;Where is Automotive Security going?&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We classify the attacks in three classes:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Penetration tests aiming to gauge the attack surface of certain cars&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Theft incidents that relate to the traditional car ownership patterns&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Circumventing legislation and cheating&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Penetration tests have been the most public visible activity in the field so far. Stories of what attackers might be able to influence and gauging what are the effects on individuals receive interest of a broad audience listening to the media channels. This year’s successful penetration tests contributed to make the autosec field visible and raise the awareness to ‘something needs to be done’, even for those manufacturers that have not yet acted.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Theft protection is the traditional application (cyber-)security technologies in vehicles. Ever since the cars can use transponders to augment the capabilities of the mechanical key, cryptography, digital communication and handling of sensitive information has been an issue in vehicles. Still, getting a car in physical possession is one of the big motivations to attackers and automotive security researchers. As the traditional mobility patterns are changing, ownership patterns are changing, too. For instance, car sharing removes the necessity to maintain a vehicle for individuals and makes mobility even more affordable through resource pooling.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The last category might indicate where the field is going to. As it is software that effects the differentiation between products, we might see more such attacks in the future. Using a hack on one’s car to get a better service is something that even good people might eventually do. Like jailbreaking a smartphone is a widespread phenomena and not restricted to a conspirative subgroup. People might even be willing to pay for such exploits.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;wrapping-up-autosec-2015&quot;&gt;Wrapping up AutoSec 2015&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The year 2015 revealed that the car makers are at different stages implementing security countermeasures in their cars. Acknowledging that any car maker could be targeted by a successful attack, it is the recovery after the attack that makes a difference to the car holder. For instance, BMW and Tesla were able to quickly react to the reported attack vectors through their remote update functions. Jeep’s hack took more effort for remediation. The year’s autosec incidents not only showed the capabilities of different manufacturers, but also indicated where the field is going to. The automotive industry is becoming a service-oriented business and as such, it will have to deal increasingly with service-oriented hacks.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Armin Wasicek</name><email>hellospencer@gmail.com</email></author><summary type="html">2015 has been an exciting year regarding automotive security. Many autosec incidents have been reported in media and thus raised public awareness for the field. Some of these incidents triggered big time events. It has been the first time that car makers were pointed out by name because of their vulnerable models. The first cyber security related callback action has happened in 2015. Exploits have been disclosed in mainstream security conferences such as Black Hat and Defcon and stirred up a discussion on ethical disclosure in automotive security.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">MODESEC Project</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/project/security/cyber-phiscal%20systems/2015/08/01/modesec_project_summary/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="MODESEC Project" /><published>2015-08-01T00:00:00-07:00</published><updated>2015-08-01T00:00:00-07:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/project/security/cyber-phiscal%20systems/2015/08/01/modesec_project_summary</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/project/security/cyber-phiscal%20systems/2015/08/01/modesec_project_summary/">&lt;p&gt;The objective of the MODESEC project is to research the interaction between modelling and security in the context of Cyber-Physical Systems. The first step towards this goal is to develop and implement a development method for secure cyber physical systems. Our innovation is to investigate on how to use models to gain insights about a system’s security.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Develop a method for the secure model-based design of a CPS&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Integrate the methodology in a model-based design tool&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Evaluate the Secure Design Methodology in a case study&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The proposed approach strives to support CPS engineers that were not trained in cyber security to implement security. This will be achieved by integrating the secure design of a CPS in the model-based design approach to design a CPS. Model-based design tools are familiar to engineers working in many different domains. Thus, our approach enables these engineers to build more secure products by lowering the entry barriers to implement cyber security mechanisms.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;system-models-and-attack-models&quot;&gt;System models and attack models&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Designing and implementing appropriate control laws is one of the major tasks when building a CPS. A CPS encompasses sensors and actuators that interface with the physical environment. The control law formulates the way inputs from the sensors are interpreted and how and when outputs to the actuators are made according to the purpose of the system. A system model encompasses models for the controller implementing a control law and the environment the controller operates in. It is standard engineering practice to use system models to explore the design space before actually building a CPS. The system model is the starting point for our secure development method. Our unique approach combines system and attack models, thus, forming a model of a system under attack.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/systemattackmodel.svg&quot; alt=&quot;Alt text&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Figure 1: Combining System and attack models forms a system under attack&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;An attack model captures potential malicious behavior. Securing a CPS ultimately deals with protecting the CPS’ interaction with the physical environment. Therefore, a CPS attack model is not only relevant for the cyber part of the CPS, but also for the physical interface of the CPS. This connection is a unique challenge and separates this research from other efforts on purely software-based computer systems. The MODESEC project investigates how attack models and system models can be combined in a meaningful manner to provide insights on the consequences of attacks in the physical domain.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;security-architecture&quot;&gt;Security architecture&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The baseline for our solution is a security architecture that encompasses preventive and reactive security mechanisms. Preventive mechanisms actively prohibit a malicious user from accessing or tempering a service, for example, firewalls, access controls, or cryptographic protocols. Reactive mechanisms target recognizing malicious activities in the system. These activities can be known a priori and be specified in a rule set or discovered during the runtime of the system. The secure model-based design method connects to both kinds of mechanisms. For instance, the designer augment modify the system with preventive mechanism such that a given attack model fails as a consequence of the modification. Or the attack model could be transformed in a specification for a reactive mechanism, thus, able to detect certain attacks.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;work-performed&quot;&gt;Work performed&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So far, the work has been dedicated to develop a secure design method and a reactive mechanism. First, it was important to learn and understand the methods and tools that a control engineer uses. Second, the concept of aspect-oriented modelling was adapted modelling the security of a system. All artifacts that constitute the secure design method have been implemented and its evaluation has been facilitated. Exemplary attack models have been implemented. A workflow that meets the work habits of control engineers has been specified. Third, an effort was made to develop principles for detecting modifications in the context of automotive systems. A novel intrusion detection approach has been developed and implemented. Finally, a significant amount of time has been dedicated to present the method at conferences, and workshops. Experts have been consulted and companies have been visited.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;main-results&quot;&gt;Main results&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The first main result has been the specification of a secure design method leveraging the concept of aspect-oriented modelling. Aspect-oriented modelling enables a designer to simulate system models and attack models at the same time and in the same modelling environment (Ptolemy II in our case).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The second main result is the development of a reactive security mechanism that monitors a system’s environment and infers, if the controller has been modified. Both results have been applied to automotive case studies.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;final-results-and-their-potential-impact&quot;&gt;Final results and their potential impact&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The goal of this research effort is a modelling approach to analyze and secure control systems with respect to security. We strive to derive a method that enables an engineer to prototype and compare different implementations within a model-based design method such that the engineer gets insights on the trade-offs for increasing the security. The final result will be a secure design method for design space exploration. It will facilitate the implementation of reactive security mechanisms particularly for the physical part of a CPS. Thus, we show how the use of models can contribute to build secure CPS. Application on automotive systems will enhance the visibility of the research, as security concerns in vehicles are currently a topic of high interest. We hope to impact the secure development of novel safety features in the design of the new generation of semi-autonomous and autonomous vehicles.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Armin Wasicek</name><email>hellospencer@gmail.com</email></author><summary type="html">The objective of the MODESEC project is to research the interaction between modelling and security in the context of Cyber-Physical Systems. The first step towards this goal is to develop and implement a development method for secure cyber physical systems. Our innovation is to investigate on how to use models to gain insights about a system’s security.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Security of Smart Cars</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/automotive/security/2015/01/08/interview_with_heute_de/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Security of Smart Cars" /><published>2015-01-08T00:00:00-08:00</published><updated>2015-01-08T00:00:00-08:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/automotive/security/2015/01/08/interview_with_heute_de</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/automotive/security/2015/01/08/interview_with_heute_de/">&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;heute.de (H)&lt;/em&gt;     On Sunday automakers will launch the international auto show in Detroit. There the cars of the future will be presented and the trend is clearly towards smart and connected vehicles. What will the smart cars be able to do?&lt;/strong&gt;*&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;armin (A)&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;      The vehicle of the future will exchange information not only with the environment but also with infrastructure systems to allow the vehicle occupant a safe and pleasant driving experience. In the discussions about the car of the future, it is so often talked about the innovative technology, but little of the people inside the car. The smart cars will assist drivers by taking over tasks that machines are better capable to solve than people.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;(H)&lt;/em&gt;     Is it technically possible that the cars of the future communicate, for example, with one another or with the environment like traffic lights or parking lots?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;(A)&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;     This is made possible by wireless communication. For example, industry experts are working right now on a communication standard called WAVE, which stands for Wireless Access in Vehicular Environments. The WAVE standard is an enhancement of wireless networks in order to meet the needs for networked cars.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;(H)&lt;/em&gt;     You have stated recently, everything that can be hacked, will hacked. How can you protect the smart cars of the future from hacker attacks?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;(A)&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;      As security researchers, we must take this stance. In my view, a suitable mix between preventive and reactive mechanisms will protect the car of the future. Preventive mechanisms for example, block unauthorized access. Reactive mechanisms aim to detect conspicuous events in the system, which then might be assigned to attacks. The proper cooperation between the two mechanisms is crucial.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;(H)&lt;/em&gt;     Also you also actively research the security of cars. What exactly are you working on?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;(A)&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;      At the moment I am concentrating my research efforts on reactive mechanisms and what particularly interests me is the manipulation of ECUs. Specifically, I’m working on a method to detect the manipulation of engine controllers.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;(H)&lt;/em&gt;     At security conferences, hackers have already demonstrated how to hack the smart cars. They have, for example, manipulated speedometer, turned on brakes or even steered the vehicle using their laptops. Is it really so easy to hack the security of smart cars?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;(A)&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;      The short answer is no. Cars as they are currently on the streets have no protection mechanisms installed, as these researchers show impressively. Technically such manipulations are quite feasible. However, there are also limitations. For the attacks illustrated the attacker would have direct access to the car have, may open the hood or access differently to the vehicle electronics. In addition, the attacker would have to know exactly the format of control messages. This format will usually differ between vehicle types. The effort to successfully attack a vehicle can be very high.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;(H)&lt;/em&gt;     What features of smart cars are particularly sensitive to attacks?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;(A)&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;      A main attack surface is secure software updates. How can you safely upgrade the software in a car? This question is a major challenge, especially if you’re including, so-called ‘over-the-air’ updates that are updates imported via a wireless connection in the car. Currently such functions are not widely deployed, but the cost savings and the possibilities such a feature would enable are huge.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;(H)&lt;/em&gt;     Will there be an absolute security against hacker attacks at smart cars at all at some point?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;(A)&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;      No, there won’t absolute security. But the current security debate helps to raise awareness for security concerns and that is a basic requirement for safe systems. It is important that a single attack cannot disrupt the entire system. Even if one single attack is successful, it should be possible to contain the damage. Which is in turn a technical problem to be solved.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;(H)&lt;/em&gt;     In your opinion, how important is the protection against hacker attacks for automakers in the development of their smart cars?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;(A)&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;      Cyber security is my perception very high on the priority list of the automakers.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;(H)&lt;/em&gt;     A current trend is towards self-driving cars, like Google, for example, has been testing for some time. Even traditional automakers like Volkswagen strive for self-driving cars. As a driver, can you just sit back and even fall asleep while the car drives by itself, or would there be a risk that hackers take control of the car?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;(A)&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;     Such an attack would quite brazenly. But seriously, it’s not so important whether the driver or the autopilot take the decisions in the car, but that attack surface the interfaces in the car are exposing.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;(H)&lt;/em&gt;     Smart devices store data to function as personalized as possible for their user. Must car holders fear that their car collects personally identifiable information and pass that on to the automakers?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;(A)&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;     The customers should not have any fear. I do not think that automakers have the intention to spy on someone or to do harm, but collect these data in order to build more efficient systems. This in turn provides benefits for the customer. The data should be anonymized and customers should ask for such features. This is also an interesting area of ongoing research.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;(H)&lt;/em&gt;     Many thanks for the interview!&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;(A)&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;     Thank you!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Interview with heute.de on January 8, 2015 (translated to English)&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Armin Wasicek</name><email>hellospencer@gmail.com</email></author><summary type="html">heute.de (H)     On Sunday automakers will launch the international auto show in Detroit. There the cars of the future will be presented and the trend is clearly towards smart and connected vehicles. What will the smart cars be able to do?*</summary></entry></feed>
